there it is Ellie
taco Bell it looks like there are three
clickers around the building
so we should be careful do you think you
can take them all
down yourself [ __ ] or do you want me to
do it
Joel I know how to shoot clickers I'm
not a little girl anymore
oh believe me Ellie I know you're not a
little girl anymore
i think I know that more than anyone
else in Jackson
Abbey watch our backs and make sure
there aren't any other infected nearby
don't tell me what to do [ __ ] I can
break your spine into
i can crush your [ __ ] head like a
meatball [ __ ]
we woke up the whole [ __ ]
neighborhood everybody get inside taco
Bell before you're fun
i can't believe we actually found a taco
Bell that is still open
after all these years I’ve been wanting
to try taco Bell tacos ever since Joel
told me about them
he says they're the [ __ ] [ __ ] I used
to bring my daughter to taco Bell all
the time
it gives me diarrhea but at least it
would make her happy
after I beat her now how about you girls
tell me what you want so we can get out
of here
before more infected show up I want
tacos shut up [ __ ]
i make the decisions around here we're
getting three crunch wrapped supremes
I’ve never had a crunchwrap supreme
before and if I like it I'm going to
take both of yours
hey [ __ ] you man you can't just decide
what we're all going to get
you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] calm your [ __ ]
tits only
this is abby's world we're just living
in it
hey have you [ __ ] ever heard about
Sonic Underground it's the [ __ ] [ __ ]
it's a cartoon about this character
named Bartleby
he has a [ __ ] named Sonic the Hedgehog
Sonic x Bartleby is [ __ ] cute
Sonic also has a brother and sister and
they're all in a rock band together
they play music and [ __ ] while they look
for their mum
the queen of Mobius who abandoned the
three of them as babies
all while fighting the evil Doctor Robotnik
and his army of swat buds
[Music]
your shadows
i would